Gus Russo papers, Inclusive: 1932-2006, Bulk: 1953-1998
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Back Channels, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Assassination Information Bureau (AIB), 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Gallup Poll on JFK Assassination, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- 1993 File ReleaseDLNational Archives and Records Administration (NARA), 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Testimony before the Committee on Governmental Affairs: Lesar, James H. and Gates, Robert M., 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Nonpartisan Consolidated Files (NCF) Working Group, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Hearings Before the Committee on Government Operations, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Shaw, Clay L., 1958, 1967, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Shaw, Clay L., Address Book, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Brooks, Jack, Files, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Hearing before the Legislation and National Security Subcommittee of the Committee on Government Operations, November 17, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Construction of the District of Columbia Stadium, and Matters Related Thereto (Part I-II) [U.S. Senate; 1 of 7], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Construction of the District of Columbia Stadium, and Matters Related Thereto (Part III) [U.S. Senate; 2 of 7], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Construction of the District of Columbia Stadium, and Matters Related Thereto (Part IV) [U.S. Senate; 3 of 7], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Construction of the District of Columbia Stadium, and Matters Related Thereto (Part V-VI) [U.S. Senate; 4 of 7], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Construction of the District of Columbia Stadium, and Matters Related Thereto (Part VII-VIII) [U.S. Senate; 5 of 7], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Construction of the District of Columbia Stadium, and Matters Related Thereto (Part IX) [U.S. Senate; 6 of 7], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Construction of the District of Columbia Stadium, and Matters Related Thereto (Part X-XI [U.S. Senate; 7 of 7], 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- The Nation, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- American University Speech, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- DiEugenio, Jim “JD” Post, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- JFK + Military, 1966, 1986, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- JFK + Federal Reserve, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Military Leads, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Dallas Motorcade Route, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Limousine/Lincoln, 1964, 1978-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- National Security Action Memorandum (NSAM) No. 273, 1961, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- NSAM No. 55, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Executive Orders, 1953, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Threats against JFK, 1961, 1963, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- JFK + Vietnam, 1961-1963, 1992, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Sprague, Films, Photos, 1964, 1967-1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- CBS Reports Inquiry: “The American Assassin”DL1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- National Security Archive, 1962, 1970, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Small, Cecil, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Sprague, Richard E., 1975-1978, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Stockwell, John, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
- SpyBASE, undated (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Sullivan, William, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Thompson, Steve, 1963, 1967-1968, 1976, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Thornley, Kerry W., 1963, 1975, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Tippit, J. D., 1963-1964, 1982, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- McMillan, Priscilla J., 1963 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Mexico Man, 1964, 1976-1977, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Milan, Michael, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Milteer, Joseph A., 1963, 1967-1968, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Moffett, Sandra, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Moody, Shearn (Jr.), 1963, 1987, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Morrow, Robert, Betrayal, 1963, 1971, 1976-1977, 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey, Diary, 1959-1962 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Martino, John, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey, Library Books, 1963-1964, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Burris, Howard L., 1956, 1961-1970, 1975, 1978, 1990-1994 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Florida Ints., 1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Lincoln, Evelyn, 1994, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Goddess: The Secret Lives of Marilyn Monroe, Notes, undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Lawford, Peter, FBI, 1937, 1947, 1950, 1954, 1960-1967, 1973, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Madden, Owney, 1963-1965, 1983, 1986-1991 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Rothmiller, Michael “Mike” J., 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Pell, Claiborne, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Document Authentication, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Blood and Power, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Huie, William Bradford, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Meyer, Mary Pinchot, 1976, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Williams, William A. H., 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Kennedy, Jr., Joseph P., 1964, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Kennedy, Joseph P., Clippings, 1963-1965, 1968-1971, 1977, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Kennedy, Trusts and Closed Records, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Kennedy, Joseph P., and Spellman, Cardinal Francis, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- McCarthy, Kerry, 1994, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Blauvelt Family and Durie Malcom, 1957, 1961-1962, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Dowd, James, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Rodgers Brothers: Harry and William “Bill”, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Malcom (Kerr), Durie, 1947, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Kennedy Family, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- O'Donnell, Kenneth “Ken”, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- JFK FBI Biography, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- “Amazing Grace,” Yacht, 1960, 1962, 1967, 1972, 1974-1977 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Spellman, Cardinal Francis, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Des Rosiers, Janet Fontaine, 1960, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Des Rosiers, Janet Fontaine, 1959-1960 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Spotts, Neil, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Swanson, Gloria May Josephine, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Niven, David, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Davies, Marion, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Rooney, Mickey, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Berle, Milton, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
- MacLaine, Shirley, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Curtis, Tony, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Lewis, Jerry, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
- (Olsson), Ann-Margret, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Smith, Keeley, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Cahn, Gloria, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Martin, Dean, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Smith, Liz, Clippings, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Summers, Anthony, Video Interviews on Say Goodbye to the President, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Harriman, Averell W., 1970, 1975, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Kennedy Spies, Victor Lasky and George Morse, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Jacobson, Dr. Max, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- JFK’s Groin Injury, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Frosch, Aaron + Lawyers, 1964-1981 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Cusak, Lawrence X., 1959-1982 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- DeLoach, Cartha “Deke”, 1957-1963, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Dog Days At the White House, Bryant, Traphes, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Metrik Case (Metrik, Simon), Clark, Alicia Purdom, 1961-1963, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Presidential Escapades, 1975-1997 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Rometsch, Ellen, 1989-1995 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Von Post, Gunilla, Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Sullivan, Michael John, Presidential Passions, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Meredith, Judy, 1952-1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Turnure, Pamela, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Purdom, Alicia, AKA Alicia Purdom Clark, 1955-1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Meyer, Mary Pinchot, 1964-1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Hitchcock, Joan, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Chang, Suzy (Keeler, Profumo, V-girl), 1963-1968 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- "Government Girls," Larry King Playboy article, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Assassination Archives and Research Center (AARC), 1988-1997 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Congress of Freedom, 1960-1971 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Kennedy, Robert F., and Monroe, Marilyn, undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
- RFK and Monroe, Clippings, 1981-1992 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Military Intelligence, 1963-1978 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Hosty, James P. (Jr.) + FBI, 1963-1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Hosty, James P. (Jr.) + FBI, Clippings (Part I and II), 1964-1998 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Hoover (J. Edgar) Memorandum, November 29, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Hoover, J. Edgar + Oil, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Hoover, J. Edgar/ Rowley (Hon. James J.) Memorandum, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Slawson, W. David/Coleman, Jr., William T., Memorandum, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
- FBI Lee Harvey Oswald Imposter Memorandum, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- FBI Documents (Rel: 1977), 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Dallas Police Files, 1952-1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Dallas Police, Fritz, Will, 1975-1984 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- FBI Spectrographic Report on President Kennedy’s Assassination, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Ruby, Jack/Nixon, Richard M. Link, 1947-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Ruby, Jack + FBI, 1959-1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Ruby, Jack, Correspondence, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Texas Original Documents, 1961-1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Ruby, Jack + Mob, 1963-1991 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Ruby, Jack, 1947-1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Ruby, Jack, Clippings, 1967-1992 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Ruby, Jack + Trafficante Family, 1954-1963 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Presidential Libraries, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Southwest Collection/ Carr, Vincent Waggoner, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- The Christic Institute (Iran Contra, etc.), 1987-1990 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- The Christic Institute, Clippings, 1987-1992 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Artichoke Project, 1954-1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Colonel X., 1948-1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Shaffer, Charles, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Warren, Earl, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Slawson, W. David on Mexico Tapes, 1964-1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Russell, Senator Richard, Dissent (Warren Commission), 1964 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Warren Commission Name Index, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Warren Commission documents, CDs released circa 1970, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Warren Commission, 1961-1993 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Warren Commission, Clippings, 1975-1997 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Logue, Lester L., 1958-1964 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Logue, Lester L., Correspondence, 1958-1964, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Ruby, Jack, Phone Books, 1963-1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Third Decade, 1984-1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Third Decade, 1991-1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Fourth Decade and Other Publications, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Bush, George, 1963-1991 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Bush, George, Clippings, 1976-1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey + Mob, 1963-1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Oswald in Atlanta and Montreal, 1963-1993 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Oswald and Drivers License, 1963-1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Oswald, Backyard Photos + L.A. Letter, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Oswald, LSD, 1983-1992 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Oswald, Pamphlets, 1961-1963 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Oswald’s 1962 Income Tax (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Oswald, Biography, undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Minox, Camera/Film, 1963-1978 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Oswald, Pravda, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Oswald Autopsy, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Oswald’s 201 Personality File (FBI), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Oswald, Death and Exhumation, 1964-1984 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Oswald + FBI, 1962-1978 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Oswald + Fellow Marines, 1963-1978 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Oswald + Ruby, Jack, 1963-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Oswald + Ruby, Jack, Clippings, 1976-1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Oswald, L.A., 1959-1969 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Oswald, Florida, 1963-1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Oswald, New Orleans, 1966-1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Oswald + Civil Air Patrol (CAP) and Ferrie, David W., 1954-1968 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- New Orleans CDs, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- New Orleans, 1962, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Informational Council of the Americas (INCA), 1963-1970 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Banister, Guy, 1954-1979 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Rodriguez, Jr., Arnesto, 1964-1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Garrison, Earling Carothers “Jim”, 1963-1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- de Brueys, Agent Warren C., 1959-1982 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Roberts, Delphine, 1962-1978 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Lewis, David F., 1963-1983 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Lewis, Ron, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Ochsner, Edward W. A. “Alton”, 1948-1992 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Pena-Alfonso, Orsetes Farnicio, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Bolton Ford Inc. Records/Receipts, 1960-1967 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Lansdale, Brigadier General Edward G., Kennedy, Robert F., 1962-1963, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Operation Solo, 1963-1966, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Operation Solo, 1956-1976 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- CIA Psychiatric Personality Study of Fidel Castro, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Hemingway, Ernest, Cuba, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Hemingway, Ernest, Cuba, 1961-2001 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- CIA’s Inspector General Report: Plots to Assassinate Castro, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Inspector General’s Survey of the Cuban Operation and Associated Documents (Part I; Cover sheet-G), 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Inspector General’s Survey of the Cuban Operation and Associated Documents (Part I; H-O), 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Inspector General’s Survey of the Cuban Operation and Associated Documents (Part I; Annexes A-E), 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Inspector General’s Survey of the Cuban Operation and Associated Documents (Part II; Cover sheet-Section III), 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Inspector General’s Survey of the Cuban Operation and Associated Documents (Part II; Section IV-Section V), 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Inspector General’s Survey of the Cuban Operation and Associated Documents (Part II; Section VI-Section VII), 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Inspector General’s Survey of the Cuban Operation and Associated Documents (Part II; Section VIII-Section IX/end), 1961-1962 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Harvey, William "Bill” King, 1967-1976, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Secret Service Statements, JFK Assassination, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Artime-Buesa, Dr. Manuel Francisco, 1963-1996 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Plots vs. Castro, 1960-1997 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Plots vs. Castro, 1961-1999 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Secret Service on Assassins, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Secret Service Assignments, 1954-1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Helms, Richard, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Phillips, David A., 1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Arehart, Arnold/Flick, Charles, 1962-1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Larson, William F., 1978 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Goodpasture, Ann + Gunn, T. Jeremy, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Goodpasture, Ann, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Hartman, Melbourne Paul, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Hidalgo, Jr., Balmes “Barney” Nives, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Horton, John, 1963-1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Angleton, James, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Wilcott, James, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Bustos-Videla, Charlotte, AKA Scaletti, Elsie I., 1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Rocca, Raymond “Ray” G. (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Rocca, Raymond “Ray” G. (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Rankin, J. Lee, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Rankin, J. Lee on Plots Against Castro, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Whitten, John a.k.a. Scelso, John, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Nosenko, Yuri Ivanovich (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Nosenko, Yuri Ivanovich (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Murphy, David E., 1978 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Hunt, E. Howard, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Solie, Bruce, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Tovar, Bernard Hugh, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Michael, James C., 1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- L.A. Elsur, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Beckham, Thomas Edward, 1960-1989 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Beckham, Thomas Edward, 1961-1990 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Sutton, James Earl; alias Files, James, 1961, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Collectors and Auctions, 1958, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- “The Secret World of Bobby Kennedy,” Article, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Kennedy, John F., Will, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Tabloids, 1964-1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Newsreal, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Wilson, Will, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Halfen, Jack H., 1957-1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Brown, Madeline, 1960-1987 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- White, Ricky, Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- “I Was Mandarin” by Gary Cartwright, Texas Monthly, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- White, Roscoe “Rocky” Anthony, 1981-1989 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- White, Ricky, FBI letter, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Walsh Report, White, Roscoe Anthony and Jordan, Phillip D., 1963-1991 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Mattox, Jim/Butler, Ned C., Letter, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Shaw, J. Gary and Harris, Larry Ray, “Codename Mandarin”, undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Forensic Document Report for People, Magazine, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- White, Roscoe Anthony, Diary, and White, Ricky, Press Kit, 1957-1990 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Anderson, Dick, Book Proposal, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
- White, Ricky + Abshire, Richard and Burke, Andy Austin + Matsu Corporation, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Waldron, Lamar, 1961-2003 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- The Tarasoffs, Boris and Anna, 1976-1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Tarasoff, Boris Dimitry, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Tarasoff, Anna, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Foreign Relations of the United States (FRUS), 1961-1963 Volume XI, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Helms, Richard M., 1963-1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Codename “Sasha”, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- CIA Institutional Fronts, 1967-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- CIA Chiefs of State and Cabinet Members of Foreign Governments: A Directory, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Dictabelts, JFK/Bob White Dictabelts, 1960, 1992-1998 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Report on Greater CIA Openness, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- CIA + Media, 1967-1977 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Dirección Federal de Seguridad (DFS), translated Federal Security Directorate, 2002-2004 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- New Cuba Research, 1959-1982, 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Bohemia, Magazine, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Dunlap, Jack, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Cobb, June, 1960-1962 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Johnson, Lyndon Banes, Tapes and Transcripts, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Arcacha-Smith, Sergio V., 1961-1999 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- 1967 Materials, 1963-1976 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Campisi, Joe, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Marcello, Carlos, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Novel, Gordon, 1976-1993 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Training Anti-Castro Units, New Orleans, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Kennedy, Robert F. + Ferrie, David and Banister, Guy, 1959-1969 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Ferrie, David, 1932-1994 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Southern Research Company Report on Ferrie, David, 1963-1980 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- New Orleans, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
- New Orleans, 1949-1992 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- New Orleans, 1963-1995 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Cubela, Rolando, 1956-1978 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Cubana Air, 1963-1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey in Cuba, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Tepedino, Carlos, 1964-1968 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Ford, Gerald and Kissinger, Henry and Scowcroft, Brent, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Mexico City Leads, 1963-1999 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Mexico Informants/Bugs, 1962-1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Mexico City, 1963-1977 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Mexico City, 1963-1996 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Mexico City, 1963-1995 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- German Television, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- CIA Budgets and JFK, 1954-1965, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey at William B. Reilly & Company Inc., 1963 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- The Dulles Family/Dulles Papers, 1954-1974 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Foreign Relations of the United States (FRUS): Cuba (1 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Foreign Relations of the United States (FRUS): Cuba (2 of 2), 1961-1963 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Oswald, Lee Harvey in Mexico, 1963-1984 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Lund, Thomas (Helms?), 1967 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Keenan, Laurence “Larry” P., 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Operation “Northwood(s)” (1 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Operation “Northwood(s)” (2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Anti-Castro Activities, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- House Select Committee on Assassinations, Lee Harvey Oswald: The CIA and Mexico City (1 of 5), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- House Select Committee on Assassinations, Lee Harvey Oswald: The CIA and Mexico City (2 of 5), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- House Select Committee on Assassinations, Lee Harvey Oswald: The CIA and Mexico City (3 of 5), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- House Select Committee on Assassinations, Lee Harvey Oswald: The CIA and Mexico City (4 of 5), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- House Select Committee on Assassinations, Lee Harvey Oswald: The CIA and Mexico City (5 of 5), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, General, 1967-1978 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, John F. Kennedy Assassination Report, Part I, by Jack Martin and David Lewis, 1961-1968 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, News Clippings, 1969, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, New Orleans, 1959-1967 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Banister, Guy, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Beaubouff, Alvin, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Claire, Ronnie, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Dalzell, William, 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Davis, Richard, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Fernandez, Fernando, 1963-1964 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Ferrie, David, 1963-1967 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Leemans, Fred H. (Garrison Bribe), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Martens, Layton, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Martin, Jack S., 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Rabel, Luis, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Roselli, Johnny, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Jim Garrison Investigation, Persons, Shaw, Clay, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Jerry Shinely Correspondence, Feb-March 1993, Section 1-Ed Butler and the Information Council of the Americas, 1956-1967 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Jerry Shinely Correspondence, Feb-March 1993, Section 2-Arcacacha-Smith and “other anti-Castro personalities”, 1960-1968 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Jerry Shinely Correspondence, Feb-March 1993, Section 3-Guy Johnson, Guy Banister, and Leander Perez, 1955-1978 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Jerry Shinely Correspondence, Feb-March 1993, Section 4- Thomas Edward Beckham, 1960-1976 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Crime of the Century: The Kennedy Assassination From a Historian’s Perspective by Michael L. Kurtz, Photocopies (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Crime of the Century: The Kennedy Assassination From a Historian’s Perspective by Michael L. Kurtz, Publications (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Flashback: The Untold Story of Lee Harvey Oswald by Ron Lewis, Publications (1 of 3), 1993 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Flashback: The Untold Story of Lee Harvey Oswald by Ron Lewis, Publications (2 of 3), 1993 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Flashback: The Untold Story of Lee Harvey Oswald by Ron Lewis, Publications (3 of 3), 1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- The Dallas Conspiracy by Peter Dale Scott, Unpublished Photocopies (1 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- The Dallas Conspiracy by Peter Dale Scott, Unpublished Photocopies (2 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- The Dallas Conspiracy by Peter Dale Scott, Unpublished Photocopies (3 of 3), 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Beyond Conspiracy: The Hidden Dimensions of the JFK Assassination by Peter Dale Scott, Paul L. Hoch, Russell Stetler, and Josiah Thompson, Photocopies (1 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Beyond Conspiracy: The Hidden Dimensions of the JFK Assassination by Peter Dale Scott, Paul L. Hoch, Russell Stetler, and Josiah Thompson, Photocopies (2 of 3), 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)